NETFLIX オリジナルシリーズ
〜
BASED ON THE COMIC SERIES
BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT
Blazing Transfer Students are agents
（天の声）
炎の転校生とは
問題がある学校に潜入し
悪を断つ
who infiltrate troubled schools
and stamp out the evil that afflicts them.
エージェントたちの
名称である
This is the story
of seven new Blazing Transfer Students.
今 ここに
新たに７人の
炎の転校生が誕生した
〜
（アンソニー）ノー
（ジルベール）ノー
（アンソニー）コマンタレヴ
How are you?
（ジルベール）ボンジュール ノー
Bonjour.
How are you? Bonjour.
コマンタレヴ　ボンジュール
-Good morning!
-Morning!
（カミヤマ）おはよう！
（シゲオカ）ち〜す
Who are they?
何や？ あいつら
CRACKLE
（フジイ）美しい
So beautiful.
What?
えっ？
So beautiful.
（フランス語で）美しい
We were destined to meet.
（フランス語で）運命の人
（日本語で）
僕たちと一緒に来てくれますね？
You'll come with us, won't you?
僕たちの学校に…
Come with us to our school.
ウイ 喜んで！
Yes. Gladly!
（シゲオカ）え？
TOSS
おい！
TOSS, PLOP
フジイ！
Fujii!
Hey!
お〜い
"Omotenashi"?
Omotenashi(おもてなし)？
（日花里(ひかり)）信じられない
How could you just stand there
and watch him being kidnapped?
連れ去られるのを
黙って見てるなんて！
（カミヤマ）
あの〜 連れ去られたっていうか…
To be exact, he wasn't kidnapped.
そう 日花里ちゃん
He's right, Hikari.
Fujii followed them voluntarily.
フジイは
自分から ついていったんや
It says this school is raising
future gentlemen.
（キリヤマ）
“未来の紳士を育てる学校”だって
（ハマダ）
なぜ“おもてなし”が
ローマ字なんだ？
Why is "Omotenashi" written in Romaji?
It's in cursive too.
（コタキ）
筆記体か… 気取ってやがるな
-They're acting classy.
-No, it's tacky.
（ナカマ）
いやいや 逆にダサいやろ
That school was only recently established.
（滝沢(たきざわ)）
そこは最近 新設された学校だが
よからぬうわさも聞いている
I've heard scandalous rumors about it.
中に入って調べてきてほしい
I'd like you to get in there
and investigate.
Also, you should rescue Fujii.
それとフジイ君の奪還
That's your mission!
それが今回のミッションよ
Us?
（カミヤマ）僕たち？
FORBIDDEN SERVICE!!
VROOM
Is this Omotenashi Academy?
ここ？ Omotenashi学園
It looks pretty amazing.
なんか すごい学校やな
うん
Why do we have to bring him back?
連れ戻してこいって…
僕 たまたま 朝
フジイ君と一緒だっただけなのに
I just happened to be with Fujii
this morning.
しょうがないんやけ
ミッションなんやし
Tough luck! It's our mission!
I don't want Hikari to think
I'm heartless.
俺も日花里ちゃんに薄情なヤツと
思われたくないねんから
Okay, let's go!
おっしゃ 行くぞ！
（ピアノの伴奏）
What a beautiful garden
（男子たち）
♪ 美しき園は
Our schoolhouse is
我らの学び舎
Young gentlemen
若き紳士が
夢を語らう
Tell of their dreams
育む心は
Our cultivated hearts
おもてなし
Treat you
もてなせば
With hospitality
When it is time
もてなすとき
もてなせよ
-To be hospitable
-Fujii!
フジイ君！
（フジイ）
♪ ああ ステキ おもてなしの心…
-Oh...
-Oh, what a hospitable heart
（中條(ちゅうじょう)）何だね？ 君たちは！
-Omotenashi Academy
-What are you doing here?
The light...
ひか…
For interrupting these pure
and sweet voices...
清らかな歌声を遮る者は
打擲(ちょうちゃく)されてもしかたがないな！
WHIP
...you deserve a whipping!
Baron Chujou!
（フジイ）バロン中條！
（中條）
どうした？ シューティングスター
What is it, Shooting Star?
（２人）シューティングスター？
-"Shooting Star"?
Please forgive them.
お許しください ムッシュウ
They are my friends.
彼らは わたくしの友人なのです
Friends?
友人？
ふむ…
They may shine if polished.
磨けば光るかもしれないな
Fine!
よろしい
At the request of beautiful Shooting Star,
美しいシューティングスターの
頼みだ
君たちも
“おもてなし紳士”として鍛えよう
I shall train you to be
Omotenashi gentlemen!
（２人）おもてなし紳士？
-"Omotenashi gentlemen"?
私は教育係のバロン中條
I am Baron Chujou.
I am a schoolmaster here.
リピート！
-Baron Chujou.
（２人）バロン… 中條…
Okay.
グッド！
Omotenashi is...
（中條）
おもてなしは
日本が世界に誇るホスピタリティだ
the Japanese hospitality
that the entire world admires.
However,
その一方で
when it comes to the treatment of women
レディファーストや
マナーについては
-and manners,
-One, two,
-we are still lacking in many areas.
-three, four, five, six...
まだまだ未熟なところが多い
そこで我が校の理念は
Our school's mission is...
to raise beautiful gentlemen.
日本の美しいジェントルメン
We raise Omotenashi gentlemen.
おもてなし紳士を
育てることにある
フフフ…
Allow me.
（フジイ）どうぞ
Thank you.
（男子）メルシー
完璧だ シューティングスター！
You're perfect, Shooting Star!
ビューティフル！
ワンダフル！
パーフェクト！
全てが… 全てが美しい！
Everything...
Everything about you is beautiful!
（生徒たちの拍手）
Baron Chujou, thank you so much.
バロン中條
メルシーボーク
Magnificent.
（中條）お見事…
-Why does he call him Shooting Star?
-I don't know.
何や？ さっきから
シューティングスターって
さあ…
Isn't this place wonderful?
すばらしい所だろう？
I desire to live beautifully,
so it's the perfect school for me.
美しく生きたいと願う わたくしに
ぴったりの学校だ
それに教育係のバロン中條も
カリスマ性があり
What's more, Schoolmaster,
Baron Chujou, is a charismatic
and attractive man.
魅力的な男性だ
Hey!
おい
We're here to take you back.
俺ら
お前を連れ戻しに来たんやで？
Also, there are scandalous rumors
about this school.
それに なんか この学校
よからぬうわさが あるらしいよ
Scandalous rumors?
よからぬうわさ？
（シゲオカ）とにかく
Anyway, let's investigate this school,
and return to Tanebi Academy together.
この学校のこと
さっさと調べて
一緒に種火学園に帰ろう
（カミヤマ）
みんな待ってるよ
-Everyone's waiting for you.
-He's right.
（アンソニー）うわ〜！
BAM
（カミヤマ）えっ？
（中條）ワーオ！
Anthony! Are you all right?
アンソニー！ 大丈夫か？
アンソニー！
Anthony!
I saw it all!
（ジルベール）僕 見ました！
These two...
この２人が
アンソニーに足をかけたんです！
tripped Anthony!
（中條）おお…
-No, no!
-What?
（カミヤマ）えっ？ いや…
（シゲオカ）え〜！
How contemptible!
何と卑劣なまねを！
What kind of gentlemen
would do such a thing?
それが紳士のすることか！
We didn't do anything!
俺ら何もしてないです
それに ２人で足をかけたって
Besides, it's impossible
for both of us to trip him.
ほら 距離的にも おかしいし…
-Look how far we're apart.
-It's impossible.
There must be some misunderstanding.
ムッシュウ 何かの間違いでは？
I will punish you both!
君たちに罰を与える
Go to the Room of Regret!
反省室に行きなさい
（シゲオカ）もう！
Darn it!
（カミヤマ）ううっ…
Yuck!
（シゲオカ）もう！
Darn it!
The Room of Regret? It's just an attic!
反省室って屋根裏部屋かよ！
ああっ もう！
Seriously?
（カミヤマ）でも どうする？
What are we going to do if Fujii says
he wants to stay at this school?
フジイ君が
この学校に残りたいって言ったら
（シゲオカ）え？
I mean, it seems like Fujii likes it here.
（カミヤマ）だって
フジイ君 妙に なじんでたし
I don't know.
（シゲオカ）どうするって…
Are you concerned about your friends?
（中條）
君の友人のことを
気にしているのかね？
ハア…
Your unhappy face is beautiful.
憂い顔も美しいな
Quit flirting with me, sir.
お戯れは おやめください
ムッシュウ
I am serious, Shooting Star.
私は本気だよ
シューティングスター
You could become the shining star
of our school.
君は この学園の輝く星となる男だ
The shining star?
輝く星？
Right.
（中條）そう
The first moment I saw you,
君を一目見た瞬間
私は そう確信した
I was convinced.
I want your beauty...
君の その美しさで
to continue to shine...
Omotenashi学園を照らし続けてくれ
at Omotenashi Academy.
（クラクション）
（カミヤマ）ん？
（女性の高らかな笑い声）
Let's see.
（カミヤマ）よいしょ
What?
えっ！
（女性の高らかな笑い声）
Why are rich ladies coming here?
なんで有閑マダムが？
行こう
Let's go!
（フジイ）ムッシュウ これは？
What is going on, sir?
This is a lesson on how to treat
women as gentlemen.
（中條）
紳士のたしなみ
レディファーストのレッスンだ
These are wealthy ladies who assist us
with the lesson.
懇意にしている有閑マダムたちに
ご協力いただいている
（潤子(じゅんこ)）オッホッホ！ バロン中條
Baron Chujou!
（中條）おお〜！
Good evening, Madam Junko!
ボンソワール マダム潤子
（潤子）
オーイエー オーイエー オホホ！
あら 新しい顔ね
Oh, you're a new face.
おお… これは お目が高い！
You have a good eye!
He started working
for Omotenashi Academy just today.
本日 Omotenashi学園に入店した
シューティングスターでございます
This is Shooting Star!
"Working"?
入店？
（潤子）オホホホホ！
I like this one! Will you escort me?
気に入ったわ
エスコートしてちょうだい
Yes! Show her to the VIP booth.
さあ ＶＩＰ席にご案内しなさい
オホホホ…
オーイエー
オー イエス イエス イエス
オ〜ッホホホ…
GLUG
（中條）
マダム潤子より
Madam Junko has provided us
with a champagne tower!
シャンパンタワー
いただきました！
I love you!
ジュ･テーム！
（男子たち）ジュ･テーム！
（拍手）
-I love you!
（潤子）オッホッホ！
（中條）
もう一度 ジュ･テーム！
Once more! I love you!
（男子たち）ジュ･テーム！
（拍手）
-I love you!
What's going on here?
何だ これは…
That is so cool!
Right? He's cute.
（カミヤマ）うわあ
熟女がいっぱい
-Look at all the mature women!
-Quit getting excited!
喜ぶなって お前
SHAKING
（中條）ジュ･テーム
I love you!
Here's a present.
（潤子）プレゾン
（中條）メルシー
Thank you.
フフフ…
（秘書）失礼いたします
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
はい
（中條）フフフ…
What's going on here?
おや？
It's too soon for you boys to be in here.
ここは 君たちには
まだ早いはずだが？
（ジルベール）いけない子ですね
Such naughty boys.
-Ouch! It hurts!
-Ouch! Hey!
（シゲオカ）痛い 痛い 痛い！
（カミヤマ）ちょっと 離して…
Ouch! Let go!
-Let go of me!
-Let go!
シゲちゃん カミカミ…
Shigeoka! Kamiyama!
You call yourselves hospitable?
何が おもてなし紳士や
生徒たちを利用して
金もうけしてるんだろ！
You're using the students to make money!
（中條）
フッフッフ… 人聞きの悪い
You make me sound evil.
That was a donation made to the school.
あれは学園への寄付金だよ
いや どう見たって あれは
おもてなしなんかじゃないやんか
-That wasn't offering hospitality.
-Hey! Look! Look!
（中條）ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
ルック ルック ルック
-Hospitality!
（３人）お　も　て　な　し
だ！
Besides, we don't think we're being used.
それに僕らも
利用されてるとは思ってないよ
We get tips, too.
チップも もらえるし
アハハハ…
（カミヤマ）何て腐った教育
What a rotten education system!
WHACK
ああっ…
If you are not going to obey me,
get out of my school!
私の言うことが聞けないなら
学園から出ていけ！
Get out!
出ていけ！
（ドアが開く音）
What are you doing, sir?
何をしているのです ムッシュウ！
How can you do this
to my lovely pair of friends?
わたくしのラブリーコンビを
こんな ひどい目に…
（カミヤマ）
ううっ… な… 何それ？
What did he just call us?
This is the lashing of love!
これは愛のむちだよ
It's an act of beautiful love
done for the sake of my students.
生徒を思う美しい愛だ
フフッ…
-Beautiful?
-Yes.
美しい？
ああ
Your beauty is a moneymaker.
君の美しさはドル箱だ
Build us a champagne tower
that can reach the sky!
これから
天にも届くシャンパンタワーを
築いていってくれ
美しくない
That is not beautiful.
ん？ シューティングスター？
Shooting Star?
（フジイ）違う！
No!
I am Kakeru Fujii,
one of the Blazing Transfer Students!
わたくしは
炎の転校生 フジイ駆(かける)だ！
（中條）あっ！
Baron Chujou,
バロン中條
I challenge you to a duel!
あなたに決闘を申し込む！
決闘？
A duel?
What you call beauty is false beauty!
There is no love in it!
あなたの言う美しさは 偽りの美だ
愛を全く感じない
I'll prove to you what true beauty is!
本当の美しさとは何か
わたくしが証明してみせる！
Really? How?
ほう… どうやって？
How?
どうやって？
You don't have a plan?
ノープランかい！
（潤子）ホ〜ッホホホ！
A duel? That sounds interesting.
決闘？ 面白そうね
Madam Junko!
（中條）マダム潤子！
How about this?
では こうしましょう
If beauty can be measured by love,
美しさを愛で測るなら
the winner should be the one who wins
the majority of our love.
私たちの愛を
より多く射止めたほうの
勝利ということで
（中條）フッフッフ…
I like it.
いいでしょう
Do you think you can defeat me,
the legendary number one host?
伝説の
ナンバーワンホストだった私に
勝てるとでも？
You were the number one host?
ナンバーワンホストやったんか
（潤子）
フッ でも今日は もう遅い
It's too late today.
My husband will be home soon.
主人が帰ってくる時間だわ
The competition will be held tomorrow.
勝負は明日よ
Okay. Make sure you get your beauty sleep.
ええ
夜は お肌を休めてください
（潤子）オッホッホ 楽しみだわ
I look forward to the duel.
オ〜ッホホホ…
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
（中條）行くぞ
（アンソニー･ジルベール）ウイ
Hey! Untie us!
（シゲオカ）おい　手 ほどいて
（カミヤマ）
シゲオカ君 シゲオカ君！
-Shigeoka! Look!
-What?
（シゲオカ）なに なに？
Here.
（カミヤマ）ちょっと これ…
（シゲオカ）えっ？ 何これ
What's this?
Fujii?
フジイ？
Come here.
It fell out of Fujii's jacket,
so I picked it up.
フジイ君の上着から落ちてるのを
拾っちゃったんだ
Was he like this before?
あいつ こんなんやったん？
He became obsessed with beauty
フジイ君 自分に
コンプレックスがあったからこそ
probably because he was insecure
about his looks.
あんなふうに 美しさに
こだわるように
なったんじゃないかな？
He wouldn't like it if he finds out
we saw this photo.
あいつさ
俺らが この写真 見たって知ったら
絶対 傷つくから
We can't tell him.
黙っとかなあかんで
うん
I want to help Fujii win tomorrow's duel.
僕… 明日の決闘
フジイ君に勝たせてあげたい
What can we do for him?
フジイのために
俺らができること…
（中條）フッ
何が決闘だ
A duel?
He can never defeat me.
私に勝てるわけもないのに
フフフ…
SLAM
ん？
What?
何だ？
む！
What's going on?
何だよ おい
BANG
おい！
Hey!
Wait! Let me out!
Stay in here until tomorrow,
and get sweaty and stinky!
このまま明日まで閉じ込めて
汗まみれの
ドロドロになればええわ！
Right! You'll be so stinky that the ladies
will hate you!
そうそう
汗臭くて マダムたちに
嫌われちゃえばいいんだ！
Hurry!
（シゲオカ）早く 早く！
-Good!
-Open up!
（中條）開けろ　開けなさい！
Open up!
THERMOSTAT: 46 DEGREES
何だ？ 暑い…
It's hot!
暑くなってきたぞ！
-It's getting hot!
-That's good!
（シゲオカ）よっしゃ よっしゃ
Hey!
（中條）おい 開けろ！
-Open up!
-My pants are falling down!
（カミヤマ）ズボンずれる
（中條）開けなさい！
Open up! I am the Baron!
私はバロンだ！
バロン中條だぞ！
I am Baron Chujou!
あ… 暑い！ 暑い！
It's hot! It's hot!
ああ！ 暑い…
Open up!
開けろ！
Throw the rose in for the one
you think is more beautiful.
（男子）
美しいと思うほうに
バラを
投げ入れてください！
（拍手）
（マダムたち）きゃ〜！
The blue rose is for Kakeru Fujii.
（男子）
青いバラは フジイ駆
The red rose is for Baron Chujou.
赤いバラは バロン中條
（拍手と歓声）
Okay!
よっしゃ…
Fujii!
フジイ！
Win this thing, and return
to Tanebi Academy with us.
絶対 勝って
一緒に種火学園に帰ろうね
-Where's Baron Chujou?
-I'll look for him.
ムッシュウは？
さ… 探してくる
Our first contestant is
では エントリーナンバー１番
Kakeru Fujii!
フジイ駆！
（歓声）
Shining Wink!
シャイニングウィンク！
（マダムたち）
きゃ〜 かっこいい！
What a stud!
Shining Roller Coaster Wink!
シャイニングコースターウィンク！
（歓声）
Shining...
シャイニング…
Tornado Wink!
トルネードウィンク！
（マダムたち）
きゃ〜！
回るわ！ 回る 回る！
（２人）
きゃ〜 かっこいい！
こっち見て〜！
-What a stud! Look at me!
-Fujii is such a stud!
続きまして
エントリーナンバー２番
Next, please welcome
our second contestant,
バロン中條！
Baron Chujou!
WHO IS MORE BEAUTIFUL?
（拍手と歓声）
OMOTENASHI ACADEMY
Baron Chujou!
バロン中條！
（マダムたち）
バロン どうしたの？
何かあったの？
-Where is he?
-Did something happen to him?
Baron Chujou?
（男子）
バロン中條？
I doubt he had time to shower.
シャワーを浴びる余裕すら
なかったやろ
He must be too stinky to come out.
汗臭くて出てこれないんだよ
（ドアが開く音）
（マダムたち）
えっ なに なに？
ええっ！ どういうこと？
What?
-Who's that?
-What?
（中條）遅れて すまねえな
-Sorry I'm late.
-Who's that?
BARON
I've just finished working
at a construction site,
ちょっくら 現場での仕事を１件
片づけてきたんだ！
and now I'm here!
Baron Chujou is dressed
like a construction worker!
バロン中條がガテン系に！
（マダム１）
わあ…
こんなムッシュウ 初めて〜！
I've never seen him like this before!
He's so manly!
（マダム２）
なんて男らしいのかしら！
（マダム３）ああ…
I love this thick, workingman's pheromone!
濃厚な働く男のフェロモン
（うっとりする声）
ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい…
No! No!
SLICE
そりゃ！ そりゃ！
そりゃ〜！
（マダムたち）きゃ〜！
SLICE
そりゃ！ そりゃ！
（マダムたち）きゃ〜！
What's going on?
（シゲオカ）何てことや！
He's using his stink to his advantage
and make himself look manly!
汗臭さを逆手に取って
男らしさに変えてしまうなんて！
Fujii is like a smooth boiled egg,
つるんとした ゆで卵のような
フジイ君に対して
but Baron Chujou is like a seasoned egg
right now!
今のバロン中條は
いわば味付け玉子！
くそ〜！
味付け玉子のほうが おいしい！
Darn it! A seasoned egg is more delicious!
Shining Wink!
シャイニングウィンク！
せいや〜！
（マダムたち）きゃ〜！
Shining Wink!
シャイニングウィンク！
せいや〜！
Shining Wink!
シャイニングウィンク…
（シゲオカ）
ああ〜 威力 弱なってる！
He's losing his power!
（中條）フッ…
What's wrong? Did you get dirt
in your eyes?
目に ほこりでも入ったのか？
What a wimpy wink you have!
何だ？
その みっともないウィンクは！
Now, for the finishing blow!
そして…
これで とどめだ！
（指を鳴らす音）
BOOM
What's that?
（マダムたち）
ええっ？
誰？ あのデブの子
-Who is that fatty?
-Who's that?
（ざわめき）
What's that?
-How did that photo get there?
-What?
（シゲオカ）なんで あの写真…
Did I drop the picture somewhere?
僕 写真 落としちゃった
（ざわめき）
What's that?
Is that...
（マダムたち）
もしかして…
ええっ？
What's that?
（中條）フフフ…
-Who's that?
-What is that picture?
How does it feel?
どうだ？
醜い自分を さらされた
惨めな気分は？
Are you enjoying how miserable it feels
to have this ugly photo of you exposed?
ハハハ…
Stop! This is cruel!
（カミヤマ）やめてよ
こんなの あんまりだよ！
Fujii worked hard to lose weight!
フジイ君 頑張って痩せたのに…
Ugly?
醜い？
I think it's beautiful.
美しいじゃないか
What?
は？
This is me, when I grew fat and beautiful
（フジイ）
これは 両親の深い愛情のもと
ぷくぷくと太り
thanks to the love of my parents.
美しかった頃の わたくしだ
はあ〜？
What?
これの
どこが美しいっていうんだ！
What's beautiful about this?
（フジイ）
何を言う？
これはこれで美しいじゃないか
What are you talking about?
This is quite beautiful.
I lost weight
only for the sake of my health.
ただ 健康上の問題で
この体型になったまでだ
戯言(ざれごと)を…
Nonsense!
ただのデブじゃないか！
You were nothing more than a fatso!
（フジイ）いや
No, I am beautiful
no matter what shape I am in.
わたくしは どんな姿でも美しい
これを見ろ
Look at this.
SWISH
FLAP
ハッ…
We didn't need to hide it from him.
別に隠したい過去でも
なかったんやな
No, I'll never accept that!
うるせえ 認めねえぞ
Who would ever say
these fat and ugly old bags beautiful?
大体 てめえ
デブ ブス 年食ったババアを
誰が美しいって言うよ？
（ざわめき）
（潤子）
ちょっと 何それ！ どういうこと？
-How rude!
-How dare he say that!
He called us old bags!
私たちのこと？
（マダムたち）
失礼な！ 失礼だわ！
-Is he serious?
-How rude!
（中條）ハッ…
（ざわめき）
Sir!
（フジイ）ムッシュウ！
There is no love...
あなたの美には 愛がない
in your beauty.
Since it has no love,
愛がないから
美に自由がないのです
your beauty has no freedom.
わたくしは
わたくしの愛した人なら
If I love someone,
I find that person beautiful
どんな姿でも 美しいと思うだろう
no matter what they look like.
There is nothing weaker
than beauty without love. However...
愛のない美しさほど
もろいものはないのです
しかし！
beauty with love lasts forever!
愛がある美しさは 永遠なのです
For all of you to live beautifully,
let's shout out our love!
皆さんも 美しく生きるために
愛を叫びましょう
I love you!
ジュ･テーム！
ああ！ ジュ･テーム！
I love you!
ジュ･テーム
-I love you!
（マダムたち）ジュ･テーム！
（歓声）
（フジイ）ありがとう
Thank you!
Kakeru Fujii's beauty lasts forever!
フジイ駆の美は永遠です
メルシー　メルシーボーク
Thank you so much!
（マダムたちがうっとりする声）
Ultimately, he loves himself the most.
結局
自分が いちばん好きってこと？
Narcissists are invincible.
ナルシストは最強やな
（拍手）
Thus, Kakeru Fujii,
the evangelist of love and beauty
（天の声）
こうして 愛と美の伝道師
もとい 炎の転校生 フジイ駆が
and a Blazing Transfer Student,
achieved victory.
勝利を収めた
After the duel, Baron Chujou incurred
the hostility of the wealthy ladies
決闘の際
マダムたちの反感を買った
バロン中條は
and was driven out of Omotenashi Academy.
Omotenashi学園を追われ
Right afterward,
the school went out of business.
それと同時に学園も消滅した
GULP
プハア…
The sweat of labor...
労働の汗…
is beautiful!
美しい！
Has Kakeru Fujii returned safely?
（滝沢）
無事 フジイ駆を連れ戻したか？
Yes.
（日花里）ええ
７人の駆君が また そろいました
All seven Kakerus are back.
（滝沢）７人のうち誰かが…
Which of these seven...
この種火学園の
重大な鍵となる人物
Who'd be the one to decide the fate
of Tanebi Academy?
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey